Adinarayana Koppala

Ameerpet, Hyderabad, Telangana adiknarayan9_nmm@indeedemail.com +9199894 62794

١

Overall experience of 9+ years in Creative Design Team. Being extremely passionate about designing and creating new ideas, I'm a keen learner who is willing to share my experiences with people around. I can claim to be good at leading and working together towards a goal. Open to constructive criticism which I believe would only make one stronger any day.

Work Experience

Senior Graphic Designer

izura private limited & KRS Group - Hyderabad, Telangana April 2022 to Present

They manufacture tower cranes, mini cranes, material hoists, and TMT processing machines.

Skills: Advertising • Logo Design • User Interface Design • Banner Designing • Web Pages • Print Design

• Digital Printing • Poster Design • Microsoft Excel • Microsoft Office • Adobe Photoshop • Microsoft PowerPoint • Graphic Design

Work Experience |

Graphic Designer

capillary technologies - Hyderabad, Telangana January 2016 to August 2019

- Project Analysis
- Documentations (Scope of work, Quality & Utilization)
- Time Management (Effort Estimation)
- Job Management
- Manage Client Expectations
- Digital Workflow Management

Projects |

- http://www.luluwebstore.com/
- http://www.urdoorstep.com/
- http://www.biba.in
- http://www.fabindia.com
- http://www.courts.com.my
- http://www.indianterrain.com/
- https://www.bestpricewholesale.co.in
- https://www.shop.zevenworld.com/
- http://www.humarashop.com/
- http://www.prestige.martjack.com/
- https://www.medsmart.co/

Graphic Designer

Reasoning Global eApplications Limited & Martjack - India

September 2012 to December 2015

- Email Template Designing
- Website Inventory Management
- Website Re-branding
- Mobile Applications Design

Education

B.F.A. in Fine Arts

Potti Sreeramulu Telugu University Hyderabad - Hyderabad, Telangana

Skills / IT Skills

- Mobile Application Design
- · Microsoft Office
- · Adobe Photoshop
- Good designing skill
- Online Advertising (Static Banners)
- Adobe Illustrator
- Faster learning
- Responsive and Interactive Design
- Ability to work with, and guide a team
- Adobe InDesign
- UI Designing
- Innovative
- Good communication skills

Online Profile

https://adiknarayan.blogspot.com

https://www.behance.net/adinarayana